Guide to the Yale University Library Subject Card Catalog
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale University Library subject card catalog
1860-1979
RU 982
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
693
(693 boxes)
The materials consist of the Yale University Library subject catalog cards, which were retrospectively converted to electronic format.
Yale University. Library
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 32-C (YRG 32-C), Records of Yale University Library departments and offices.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The materials were transferred from the Yale University Library, 2005.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged alphabetically by subject term.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of the Yale University Library subject catalog cards, which were retrospectively converted to electronic format.
Library catalogs; Yale University. Library -- Catalogs
- Subject cards, circa 1860-1979; Accession 2006-A-001
  - AALL-Accountability (Box 1)
  - Accountants to Actors--J (Box 2)
  - Actors--J (cont'd) to Admirals--G (Box 3)
  - Admirals--G (cont'd) to Aerial photography in soil surveys (Box 4)
  - Aerial Reconnaissance to Aesthetics (Box 5)
  - Aesthetics (cont'd) to Africa--D (Box 6)
  - Africa--D (cont'd) to Africa--S (Box 7)
  - Africa--S (cont'd) (Box 8)
  - Africa--S (cont'd) to Afro-American newspapers (Box 9)
  - Afro-American newspapers--B to Afro-Americans--H (Box 10)
  - Afro-Americans--H (cont'd) to Aged--G (Box 11)
  - Aged--H to Agricultural innovations--C (Box 12)
  - Agricultural innovations--C (cont'd) to Agriculture--E (Box 13)
  - Agriculture--E (cont'd) (Box 14)
  - Agriculture--E (cont'd) to Agriculture (by locality)--H (Box 15)
  - Agriculture (by locality)--H (cont'd) to Agriculture, Cooperative--K (Box 16)
  - Agriculture, Cooperative--L to Air warfare (Box 17)
  - Air warfare--B to Alchemy (Box 18)
  - Alchemy (cont'd) to Algeria--P (Box 19)
  - Algeria--P (cont'd) to Almanacs, American (Box 20)
  - Almanacs, American (cont'd) to America--A (Box 21)
  - America--A (cont'd) to American fiction--A (Box 22)
  - American fiction--B to American literature--19thc. (Box 23)
  - American literature--19thc. (cont'd) to American poetry--P (Box 24)
  - American poetry--P (cont'd) to Amphibians (Box 25)
  - Amphibians--A to Anecdotes (Box 26)
  - Anecdotes (cont'd) to Animal populations (Box 27)
  - Animal populations--A to Anthropo-geography--C (Box 28)
  - Anthropo-geography--C (cont'd) to Antiprotons--C (Box 29)
  - Antipsychiatry to Aquaculture--U (Box 30)
  - Aquae Sextiae to Arabic literature--A (Box 31)
  - Arabic literature to Arbitration, international (Box 32)
  - Arbitration, international (cont'd) to Architecture--D (Box 33)
  - Architecture--E to Architecture (by locality)--S (Box 34)
  - Architecture (by locality)--S (cont'd) to Architecture, Modern--18thc. (Box 35)
  - Architecture, Modern--19thc. to Arctic regions (Box 36)
  - Arctic regions--A to Argentine Republic--H (Box 37)
  - Argentine Republic--H (cont'd) to Arithmetic--E (Box 38)
  - Arithmetic--F to Art--A (Box 39)
  - Art--A (cont'd) to Art (by locality)--A (Box 40)
  - Art (by locality)--A (cont'd) to Art (by locality)--R (Box 41)
  - Art (by locality)--R to Art, Egyptian (Box 42)
  - Art, Egyptian (cont'd) to Art, Modern--20thc. (Box 43)
  - Art, Modern--20thc. (cont'd) to Art industries and trade--I (Box 44)
  - Art industries and trade--J to Artists, Expatriate--U (Box 45)
  - Artists, Finnish to Aryans--H (Box 46)
  - Aryans--R to Asia, Southeastern--C (Box 47)
  - Asia, Southeastern--C (cont'd) to Assyriology--U (Box 48)
  - Assyro-Babylonian architecture to Astronomy--P (Box 49)
  - Astronomy--P (cont'd) to Atlases--1890 (Box 50)
  - Atlases--1891 to Atomization (Box 51)
  - Atoms to Australia--E (Box 52)
  - Australia--E (cont'd) to Austria--F (Box 53)
  - Austria--F (cont'd) to Authors, American--19thc. (Box 54)
  - Authors, American--19thc. (cont'd) to Authors, French--18thc. (Box 55)
  - Authors, Low German to Authors, Russian--20thc. (Box 56)
  - Authors, Russian--20thc. (cont'd) to Automobiles--C (Box 57)
  - Automobiles--C to Bacteria, Nitrifying--C (Box 58)
  - Bacteria, Pathogenic to Balkan Peninsula--P (Box 59)
  - Balkan Peninsula--P to Banking, Interstate (Box 60)
  - Banking law to Banks and banking--P (Box 61)
  - Banks and banking--R to Baroque literature--P (Box 62)
  - Barossa Valley to Bearings (Machinery)--B (Box 63)
  - Bearn, France to Belgrad region (Serbia)--D (Box 64)
  - Belgrano (Buenos Aires, Argentina)--H to Beth-She'arim, Palestine (Box 65)
  - Beth-zur, Palestine to Bibliography--P (Box 66)
  - Bibliography--P (cont'd) to Biochemistry (Box 67)
  - Biological chemistry--A to Biology--L (Box 68)
  - Biology--M to Birds--U (Box 69)
  - Birds--U (cont'd) to Black theology (Box 70)
  - Black Theology--A to Body fluids--C (Box 71)
  - Body, Human, in literature--C to Bolton, Eng. (Yorkshire)--H (Box 72)
  - Bolton, Mass. to Bookbinding--B (Box 73)
  - Bookbinding--C to Bordeaux--H (Box 74)
  - Bordeaux--I to Botany--H (Box 75)
  - Botany--H (cont'd) to Botany (by locality)--P (Box 76)
  - Botany (by locality)--Q to Brain drain--W (Box 77)
  - Brain research to Brazil--H (Box 78)
  - Brazil--H (cont'd) to Brazil, Northeast--E (Box 79)
  - Brazil, Northeast--E (cont'd) to British in India (Box 80)
  - British--I to Buccaneers--F (Box 81)
  - Bucchero (pottery) to Buddhist logic--H (Box 82)
  - Buddhist mantras to Building trades--S (Box 83)
  - Building trades (by locality)--B to Buraku People (Box 84)
  - Buraku People--A to Business--P (Box 85)
  - Business--P (cont'd) to Byzantine Empire--B (Box 86)
  - Byzantine Empire--C to Calculus, Differential (Box 87)
  - Calculus, Differential--A to California--P (Box 88)
  - California--R to Campaign literature, 1844--D (Box 89)
  - Campaign literature, 1844--W to Canada--F (Box 90)
  - Canada--F (cont'd) to Canadian literature--20thc. (Box 91)
  - Canadian literature--20thc. (cont'd) to Cape Verde (Box 92)
  - Cape Verde--B to Capri (Tribe) (Box 93)
  - Caprifoliaceae to Carols, Provençal, Modern--V (Box 94)
  - Carols, Romanian--H to Catalan imprints (Box 95)
  - Catalan language to Catholic Church in China (Box 96)
  - Catholic Church in Chios (Island) to Cattle--B (Box 97)
  - Cattle--C to Celtis occidentalis (Box 98)
  - Celts to Chachoengsao, Thailand--S (Box 99)
  - Chaco (Argentina)--B to Charity laws and legislation (Jewish law) (Box 100)
  - Charity organization to Chemistry (Box 101)
  - Chemistry (cont'd) to Chemistry, Organic (Box 102)
  - Chemistry, Organic (cont'd) to Chess--T (Box 103)
  - Chess--V to Child study (cont'd) (Box 104)
  - Child study (cont'd) to Children--R (Box 105)
  - Children--S to Chile--E (Box 106)
  - Chile--E (cont'd) to China--A (Box 107)
  - China--A (cont'd) to China--D (Box 108)
  - China--D (cont'd) to China--F (Box 109)
  - China--F (cont'd) to China--H (cont'd) (Box 110)
  - China--H (cont'd) (Box 111)
  - China--H (cont'd) to China--I (Box 112)
  - China--I (cont'd) to China--P (cont'd) (Box 113)
  - China--P (cont'd) to Chinese characters (Box 114)
  - Chinese characters to Chinese language--C (Box 115)
  - Chinese language--D to Chinese language--T (Box 116)
  - Chinese language--T to Chinese literature--20thc. (Box 117)
  - Chinese literature--20thc. (cont'd) to Chippewa Indians--E (Box 118)
  - Chippewa Indians--F to Christian life--A (Box 119)
  - Christian life--B to Christianity and other religions--G (Box 120)
  - Christianity and other religions--H to Church and education--G (Box 121)
  - Church and education--G to Church architecture (Box 122)
  - Church architecture (cont'd) to Church music--C (Box 123)
  - Church music--C (cont'd) to Cities and towns (Box 124)
  - Cities and towns (cont'd) to Cities and towns, Medieval--F (Box 125)
  - Cities and town, Medieval--G to Civics (Box 126)
  - Civics (cont'd) to Civil service--G (Box 127)
  - Civil service--G (cont'd) to Civilization, Greek (Box 128)
  - Civilization, Greek to Classical drama (Comedy)--H (Box 129)
  - Classical education to Climatic zones (Box 130)
  - Climatology to Coast changes (Box 131)
  - Coast changes--A to Coke County, Tex.--A (Box 132)
  - Coke industry to College teachers--M (Box 133)
  - College teachers--N to Colombian essays (Box 134)
  - Colombian fiction to Combustion (Box 135)
  - Commercial law--A to Commercial policy--A (Box 136)
  - Commercial policy--B to Communism (Box 137)
  - Communism (cont'd) to Communism (by locality)--C (Box 138)
  - Communism (by locality) --C (cont'd) to Communism (by locality)--S (Box 139)
  - Communism (by locality)--S (cont'd) to Communist countries--E (Box 140)
  - Communist countries--F to Community development--J (Box 141)
  - Community development--K to Composition (Art)--A (Box 142)
  - Composition (Music) to Confederate States of America--B (Box 143)
  - Confederate States of America--C to Consciousness (Box 144)
  - Consciousness (cont'd) to Consumers--A (Box 145)
  - Consumers--B to Cookery, Chinese (Box 146)
  - Cookery, Chinese (cont'd) to Copyright (Box 147)
  - Copyright--A to Corporations--I (Box 148)
  - Corporations--M to Cosmochemistry--C (Box 149)
  - Cosmogony to Costume (Box 150)
  - Costume (cont'd) to Country life--R (Box 151)
  - Country life--S to Creation (Literary, artistic, etc.) (Box 152)
  - Creation (Literary, artistic, etc.)--A to Crime and criminals--G (Box 153)
  - Crime and criminals--G (cont'd) to Criminal psychology (Box 154)
  - Criminal psychology (cont'd) to Croatian literature--H (Box 155)
  - Croatian literature--H to Cuba--E (Box 156)
  - Cuba--E (cont'd) to Cultus, Aryan (Box 157)
  - Cultus, Assyro-Babylonian to Cybernetics (Box 158)
  - Cybernetics (cont'd) to Czechoslovakia--E (Box 159)
  - Czechoslovakia--E (cont'd) to Dakota language--R (Box 160)
  - Dakota language--T to Dead bodies (Jewish law) (Box 161)
  - Dead bodies (Law) to Decimal systems (Box 162)
  - Decimas to Delaware--E (Box 163)
  - Delaware--G to Denmark--B (Box 164)
  - Denmark--C to Detective and mystery stories (Box 165)
  - Detective and mystery stories (cont'd) to Dialectic (Box 166)
  - Dialectic to Differential equations--A (Box 167)
  - Differential equations--C to Disarmament (Box 168)
  - Disarmament--A to Dissertations, Academic--S (Box 169)
  - Dissertations, Academic--G to Domestic animals, Effect of radiation on (Box 170)
  - Domestic drama, English--H to Drama--H (Box 171)
  - Drama--I to Drug abuse (Box 172)
  - Drug abuse--A to Dutch literature--H (Box 173)
  - Earths, Rare--S to East Asia--D (Box 174)
  - East Asia--D (cont'd) to Eastern question (Far East) (Box 175)
  - Eastern question (Far East) (cont'd) to Economic assistance, Domestic--U (Box 176)
  - Economic assistance, Domestic--U (cont'd) to Economic forecasting--Y (Box 177)
  - Economic geography to Economic policy (Works pub. 1939-1960) (Box 178)
  - Economic policy (Works pub. 1939-Â \) to Economics (Works pub. 1919-1938) (Box 179)
  - Economics (Works pub. 1919-1938) to Economics--P (Box 180)
  - Economics--P to Education (Box 181)
  - Education (cont'd) to Education--F (Box 182)
  - Education--F (cont'd) to Education (by locality)--C (Box 183)
  - Education (by locality)--C (cont'd) to Education (by locality)--I (Box 184)
  - Education (by locality)--I (cont'd) to Education (by locality)--S (Box 185)
  - Education (by locality)--S (cont'd) to Education, Higher (Box 186)
  - Education, Higher (cont'd) to Education, Secondary--O (Box 187)
  - Education, Secondary--P to Educational innovations (Box 188)
  - Educational innovations--A to Educational tests and measurements--U (Box 189)
  - Educational tests and measurements--V to Egypt--H (Box 190)
  - Egypt--H (cont'd) to Election law--A (Box 191)
  - Election law--H to Electric currents (Box 192)
  - Electric Currents--G to electrochemistry (Box 193)
  - Electrochemistry--A to Elevators--L (Box 194)
  - Eleventh century--C to Eminent domain (Box 195)
  - Eminent domain--B to Encyclopedias and dictionaries (Box 196)
  - Encyclopedias and dictionaries (cont'd) to Engineering (Box 197)
  - Engineering (cont'd) to English diet drink (Box 198)
  - English drama to English fiction--20thc. (Box 199)
  - English fiction--20thc. (cont'd) to English language -D (Box 200)
  - English language--D (cont'd) to English language--R (Box 201)
  - English language--R (cont'd) to English literature (Box 202)
  - English literature (cont'd) to English literature--Y (Box 203)
  - English literature (Middle English) to English poetry (Box 204)
  - English poetry (cont'd) to English poetry--18thc. (Box 205)
  - English poetry--19thc. to Enterprise zones--U (Box 206)
  - Entertainers to Epic poetry, Russian--T (Box 207)
  - Epic poetry, Sanskrit--H to Eschatology--B (Box 208)
  - Eschatology--C to Ethics (Box 209)
  - Ethics (cont'd) to Ethiopia--H (Box 210)
  - Ethiopia--H (cont'd) to Ethnology--C (Box 211)
  - Ethnology--C (cont'd) to Ethnology--V (Box 212)
  - Ethnology--W to Europe--D (Box 213)
  - Europe--D (cont'd) to Europe--H (Box 214)
  - Europe--H (cont'd) to Europe--P (cont'd) (Box 215)
  - Europe--P (cont'd) to Europe, Northern--N (Box 216)
  - Europe, Northern--P to Evolution--B (Box 217)
  - Evolution--C to Executives (Box 218)
  - Executives--A to Eye (Box 219)
  - Eye to Family (Box 220)
  - Family--A to Farm manure as feed (Box 221)
  - Farm mechanization to Fathers in the Bible--A (Box 222)
  - Fathers of the church to Feminism and literature--U (Box 223)
  - Feminism and motion pictures to Fiber bundles (Mathematics) (Box 224)
  - Fiber optics to Finance--A (Box 225)
  - Finance--A(cont'd) to Finance--S (Box 226)
  - Finance--S (cont'd) to Financial institutions--J (Box 227)
  - Financial institutions--K to Fiscal policy--T (Box 228)
  - Fiscal policy--U to Fishes (Box 229)
  - Fishes (cont'd) to Flemish language--D (Box 230)
  - Flemish language--E to Flying squirrels (Box 231)
  - Flysch to Folk-songs, Finnish (Box 232)
  - Folk-songs, Finnish--H to Folk-lore--G (Box 233)
  - Folk-lore--G (cont'd) to Fonseca, Gulf of (Box 234)
  - Fontevrault-l'Abbaye, France to Forced labor--C (Box 235)
  - Forced labor--E to Forests and forestry--A (Box 236)
  - Forests and forestry--A (cont'd) to Fourth of July orations (Box 237)
  - Fourth of July orations (cont'd) to France--C (cont'd) (Box 238)
  - France--C (cont'd) to France--F (cont'd) (Box 239)
  - France--F (cont'd) to France--H (cont'd) (Box 240)
  - France--H (cont'd) (Box 241)
  - France--H (cont'd) to France--P (cont'd) (Box 242)
  - France--P(cont'd) to Frankfurt school of sociology (Box 243)
  - Frankfurt school of sociology--A to French drama--16thC. (Box 244)
  - French drama--17thC. to French language--E (Box 245)
  - French language--E (cont'd) to French language (by period)--20thC. (Box 246)
  - French language in Africa to French literature (by period)--19thC. (Box 247)
  - French literature (by period)--20thC. to Friends in the United States (Box 248)
  - Friendship to Frustration (Child psychology) (Box 249)
  - Fryeburg, Me. to Furniture (Box 250)
  - Furniture--A to Game theory (Box 251)
  - Game theory (con'td) to Gases, Kinetic theory of -M (Box 252)
  - Gases, Rare to Genetic engineering--C (Box 253)
  - Genetic engineering--D to Geography--P (Box 254)
  - Geography--R to Geology (by locality)--B (Box 255)
  - Geology (by locality)--B (cont'd) to Geology, Economic--Y (Box 256)
  - Geology, Stratigraphic to Georgetown Co., S.C. (Box 257)
  - Georgia to German language--D (Box 258)
  - German language--D (cont'd) to German language--S (Box 259)
  - German language--S (cont'd) to German literature--H (Box 260)
  - German literature--H (cont'd) to German literature in foreign countries (Box 261)
  - German literature (by locality)--F to Germanic languages--S (Box 262)
  - Germanic languages--T to Germany--C (Box 263)
  - Germany--C (cont'd) to Germany--F (cont'd) (Box 264)
  - Germany--F (cont'd) to Germany--H (cont'd) (Box 265)
  - Germany--H (cont'd) to Germany--P (cont'd) (Box 266)
  - Germany--P (cont'd) to Germany, West--E (Box 267)
  - Gerrmany, West--E to Gift-books (Annuals, etc.) (Box 268)
  - Gift-books (Annuals, etc.) (cont'd) to Gochevo, Russia (Box 269)
  - God to Gongorism (Box 270)
  - Gongorism (cont'd) to Graffiti--F (Box 271)
  - Graffiti--G to Gravitational radiation--M (Box 272)
  - Gravity to Great Britain--C (cont'd) (Box 273)
  - Great Britain--C (cont'd) to Great Britain--D (Box 274)
  - Great Britain--D (cont'd) to Great Britain--F (cont'd) (Box 275)
  - Great Britain--F (cont'd) to Great Britain--H (cont'd) (Box 276)
  - Great Britain--H (cont'd) (Box 277)
  - Great Britain--H (cont'd) to Great Britain--P (cont'd) (Box 278)
  - Great Britain--P (cont'd) to Great Britain--S (cont'd) (Box 279)
  - Great Britain--S (cont'd) to Greece, Modern--D (Box 280)
  - Greece, Modern--D (cont'd) to Greek language--S (Box 281)
  - Greek language--T to Greenland--M (Box 282)
  - Greenland--P to Guayaquil--G (Box 283)
  - Guayaquil--H to Hachijo Island (Japan)--H (Box 284)
  - Hachijo Island (Japan)--S to Hanafis (Box 285)
  - Hanafis--B to Hat trade--U (Box 286)
  - Hat Yai, Thailand to Hebrew imprints--V (Box 287)
  - Hebrew language to Helping behavior (Box 288)
  - Helping behavior--A to Hesychasm (Box 289)
  - Hesychasm--A to Hindustani fiction--H (Box 290)
  - Hindustani handbook to Historiography (Box 291)
  - Historiography (cont'd) to History--P (cont'd) (Box 292)
  - Historical research to Holocaust, Jewish (1939-1945) (Box 293)
  - Holocaust, Jewish (1939-1945)--ATo Honduras--D (Box 294)
  - Honduras--E to Horses--P (Box 295)
  - Horses--S to Housing--G (Box 296)
  - Housing--G (cont'd)Â to Human dissection (Box 297)
  - Human ecology to Hungarian imprints--Y (Box 298)
  - Hungarian language to Hunsruck, Ger.--S (Box 299)
  - Hunt County, Tex.--G to Hydrcarina (Box 300)
  - Hydriae to I.B.M. supai jiken no zenbo (Box 301)
  - I-chen hsien (Kiangsu Province, China)--H to Illegitimacy (Box 302)
  - Illegitimacy--B to Imaginary wars and battles (Box 303)
  - Imagination to Incentives in industry (Box 304)
  - Incentives in industry--A to Incunabula--B (Box 305)
  - Incunabula--B (cont'd) to India--E [subject cards for "Incunabula in Yale Library" were discarded after recon project by Rare Book Team] (Box 306)
  - India--E (cont'd) to India--P (Box 307)
  - India to Indians--A (Box 308)
  - Indians--A (cont'd) to Indians--N (cont'd) (Box 309)
  - Indians--N (cont'd) to Indians of Mexico--A (Box 310)
  - Indians of Mexico--A (cont'd) to Indians of North America (by locality)--C (Box 311)
  - Indians of North America (by locality)--C (cont'd) to Indians of South America--G (Box 312)
  - Indians of South America--H to Individuality (Box 313)
  - Individuality--A to Indonesia--H (Box 314)
  - Indonesia--H (cont'd) to Indus River Watershed (Box 315)
  - Indus script to Industrial management--R (Box 316)
  - Industrial management--S to Industrial sociology--A (Box 317)
  - Industrial sociology--B to Industry and state--U (Box 318)
  - Industry and state--U to Information theory in chemistry (Box 319)
  - Information theory in economics to Inscriptions, Greek (Box 320)
  - Inscriptions, Greek (cont'd) to Insects--F (Box 321)
  - Insects--G to Insurance, Marine--P (Box 322)
  - Insurance, Marine--P (cont'd) to Interest and usury (Box 323)
  - Interest and usury (cont'd) to International business enterprises--M (Box 324)
  - International business enterprises--N to International law (Box 325)
  - International law (cont'd) to International relations literature--A (Box 326)
  - International relations societies to Investments--C (Box 327)
  - Investments--E to Iran--C (Box 328)
  - Iran--C (cont'd) to Ireland--H (Box 329)
  - Ireland--H (cont'd) to Iron industry and trade--C (Box 330)
  - Iron industry and trade--D to Islam--M (Box 331)
  - Islam--O to Islands of the Pacific--H (Box 332)
  - Islands of the Pacific--N to Istria--D (Box 333)
  - Istria--E to Italian literature--H (Box 334)
  - Italian literature--H (cont'd) to Italic peoples--A (Box 335)
  - Italic peoples--C to Italy--F (Box 336)
  - Italy--G to Italy--P (Box 337)
  - Italy--P (cont'd) to Jakarta (Indonesia)--B (Box 338)
  - Jakarta (Indonesia)--C to Japan--C (Box 339)
  - Japan--C (cont'd) to Japan--E (cont'd) (Box 340)
  - Japan--E (cont'd) to Japan--H (Box 341)
  - Japan--H (cont'd) (Box 342)
  - Japan--H (cont'd) to Japan--P (cont'd) (Box 343)
  - Japan--P (cont'd) to Japanese (by locality)--B (Box 344)
  - Japanese (by locality)--B (cont'd) to Japanese language--P (Box 345)
  - Japanese language--P (cont'd) to Japanese poetry (Box 346)
  - Japanese poetry--D to Jesuits--B (Box 347)
  - Jesuits--C to Jewish literature--G (Box 348)
  - Jewish literature--H to Jews--H (Box 349)
  - Jews--H (cont'd) to Jews (by locality)--E (Box 350)
  - Jews (by locality)--E (cont'd) to Jews in Sicily (Box 351)
  - Jews in Sicily (cont'd) to Jordan--D (Box 352)
  - Jordan--E to Judaism (Box 353)
  - Judaism (cont'd) to Judicial review of administrative acts--V (Box 354)
  - Judicial sales--J to Kabuki (Box 355)
  - Kabuki--A to Kashmir--D (Box 356)
  - Kashmir--E to Khinalugh language (Box 357)
  - Khitan Mongols to Knights and knighthood--B (Box 358)
  - Knights and knighthood--F to Korea--E (Box 359)
  - Korea--F to Kuanyama (African people)--E (Box 360)
  - Kuanyama language--D to Labor and laboring classes (by locality)--A (Box 361)
  - Labor and laboring classes (by locality)--B to Labor and laboring classes (by locality)--M (Box 362)
  - Labor and laboring classes (by locality)--M (cont'd) to Labor disputes--I (Box 363)
  - Labor disputes--J to Labor supply--G (Box 364)
  - Labor supply--H to Lancashire, Eng.--G (Box 365)
  - Lancashire, Eng.--H to Land tenure (Roman law) (Box 366)
  - Land tenure--A to Land tenure--S (Box 367)
  - Land tenure--T to Language and languages (Box 368)
  - Language and languages (cont'd) to Languages, Modern--A (Box 369)
  - Language, Modern--B to Latin America--C (Box 370)
  - Latin America--D to Latin America--P (Box 371)
  - Latin America--P (cont'd) to Latin language--H (Box 372)
  - Latin language--I to Latin literature, Medieval and modern (Box 373)
  - Latin literature, Medieval and modern (cont'd) toLaw (by locality)--B (Box 374)
  - Law (by locality)--C toÂ Law (by locality)--V (Box 375)
  - Law (by locality)--W to Learned institutions and societies--H (Box 376)
  - Learned institutions and societies--I to Legends--R (Box 377)
  - Legends--S to Lepidoptera (Box 378)
  - Lepidoptera--A to Libertinism (Box 379)
  - Libertinism--A to Libraries--F (Box 380)
  - Libraries--F (cont'd) to Library science--A (Box 381)
  - Library science--A (cont'd) to Lime Springs (Iowa) (Box 382)
  - Lime-sulphur to Liquor laws--I (Box 383)
  - Liquor laws--K to Literature--H (Box 384)
  - Literature--H (cont'd) to Literature, Comparative (by locality)--A (Box 385)
  - Literature, Comparative (by locality)--B to Literature, Medieval--B (Box 386)
  - Literature, Medieval--C to Literature and society (Box 387)
  - Literature and society--A to Lobbying--W (Box 388)
  - Lobbyists to Locomotive sparks (Box 389)
  - Locomotive to London--A (Box 390)
  - London (England)--B to Lord's supper--B (Box 391)
  - Lord's supper--C to Lowenthal, Edith--A (Box 392)
  - Lower Austria to Macedonia--H (Box 393)
  - Macedonia--H (cont'd) to Mafjar (Box 394)
  - Mafulus to Malawi--A (Box 395)
  - Malawai--B to Malmo, Sweden--W (Box 396)
  - Malnutrition to Man--O (Box 397)
  - Man--P to Manchuria (Box 398)
  - Manchuria (cont'd) to Manuscripts--C (Box 399)
  - Manuscripts, Aramaic to Manuscripts, German--G (Box 400)
  - Manuscripts, German--H to Maps (Box 401)
  - Maps--B to Marisa cornuariettis (Box 402)
  - Marital counseling to Marriage customs and rites (Box 403)
  - Marriage customs and rites--U to Marxian economics--A (Box 404)
  - Marxian economics--A (cont'd) to Massachusetts--H (Box 405)